[music]
[музыка]
im instilled with a supply of 1 drop of sochi I’m
им привит поставка в 1 каплю сочи мне
fine a little and you bottom
нормально чуть и вы дно
means the group wants order and everyone who
значит хочет группа порядок и всех кто
wants chat roulette today so today on
хочет сегодня чат-рулетку так сегодня на
being tarlock in me today and yesterday and
будучи тарлок в я сегодня и вчера и
today us  tilt zoho plans but you are us
сегодня нас тильте zoho планы но вы нам
and kind of zbroi mikhail ukraine i want 7
и вид зброи михаил украинаищу я хочу 7
bright today's broadcast
пресветлые сегодняшний эфир
live interpretation
живому толкованию
persuasion of not wild let's say a new creation of
уговоры не диких скажем новым творением
wild tortured so there is still important yours you
диких пытали так там еще важную ваш вы
his
его
whole nation to experience and mihai little
всей нации переживать и михай маленькик
rocky rivers and you can do it because he himself is from
рокки реки и можно так потому что сам из
such  small terms and it turns out
таких маленьких cроки и складывается
honestly it was honestly the god of the whole nation
было честно было честно бога всей нации
so there
так там
in Russian say give war to those who are waiting for the steering wheel of
по-русски скажи дать войны кто ждет руле
points you can leave today there
точек можете уходить сегодня рулеток не
will be no roulettes today
будет сегодня
inspired by the viewing of yesterday
воодушевившись просмотром вчерашних
's today's events at the front where the armor of the
сегодняшних событий на фронте где брони
forces of Ukraine gives just such unreal stars to the
силы украины дают просто таких звездюлей
Nazis I want to
нереальных фашистам я хочу чтобы мы
today we talked live, talked,
сегодня поговорили в живу пообщались по
answered some questions in
отвечали на некоторые вопросы про запас
reserve, empathized together with the events
по сопереживали вместе тем событиям
that are taking place
которые происходят историческим событием
this is a very, very important historical event, today it will not be
это очень-очень важно сегодня не будет
any friendlier than glued accounting, so today
ни дружнее клееным учетом так сегодня у
we would even have a plus sign delivered to you in the back,
нас бы даже в спинку вами поставкой
then who is afraid of such a format
плюсик то кому куда боится такие формат
for today minus 2 on them, at least I’ll hit
на сегодня минус 2 на их то хоть и вмажу
this roulette and everyone put a plus sign who are
этом рулетку и все поставьте плюсик кто
satisfied  in such a
довольны таким
format for today, minus who is
форматом на сегодня минус кто
disappointed who wanted roulette there,
разочарован кто хотел там именно рулетку
and then I
и тогда я
love it, and
обожаю еще и
here are the cool moments and the trail, the trail will talk
вот моменты cool и тропа тропа поговорят
and I live there
и в живу там еще
to masturbate and plow the church thousand
его [__] и церкви пахать тыс
yesterday today a bunch of 2 st was and again on a
вчера сегодня куча 2 ст был и снова на
regular but a kilogram will fly in channels
регулярного но влетит килограмм каналы
gave a show Rusnya wad and so like they have a
дaвaлo шоу [__] пыж и так як у них
hollow it is
полая это
to get to the rash I
достать до сыпь мне
breathed in so you mean
надышал так-то ты разумеешь
let's say ginger and buy the empire tsik
скажем имбирь и купится империя цик
colossus on clay feet
колосс на глиняных ногах
they say about him that you are NATO's second
про него говорят что вы нато вторая
army miracle and we also had Russia
армия miracle и у нас было еще россию
called the 2nd army of the world  and she was cleaning up in
называли 2 армия мира и она убиралась в
ukraine there pict ivan then a t b a t p and
украине там пикте иван тогда а т б р а т
driving into the bay is not yet somehow
загонять в залив не еще как-то
knocked out so still the Russian army on May 3
выбивается так еще российская армия 3
Ukrainian army, they
якова из украинской армии они нас
considered us some kind of
считали какими-то
America, they are fighting for some kind of khokhlov from
америка они воюют к каким-то хохлам от
grips grandfather khokhlovka long just
grips дед хохловка длинных просто типа
like this floor is some kind of niche people like
как это этаж какието ниши люди так вроде
for the metro are not lads and girls kind of
для метро не хлопчики и девчата вид
mushroom
гриба
Andrey look in compressed in black leave
андрей посмотрите в сжатые в блэк уйти
on the channel about said  you know
на канале про сказал карается знаешь что
what happened to our people they did and
же стало с нашим народом делали и делать
want to do circus figure starline than this one on the
хотят цирковые цифра starline чем эта на
water and should watch it on this
воде и должен посмотреть и на этом
channel as well, yes, if the new ones about the
канале так ну да если новые насчет
Queen of
померла королева
Great Britain died
великобритании
in the shade, well, this is my husband shod and give ketones to the
в тени ну это муж обул и дайте в кетоны
show nab varla why are they  not that, in short,
шоу nab варла почему они не то короче
fake twitter wrote it just
фейковый twitter написал всего
reminded me of the imperious one at a time and it’s given you
напоминало властная за раз и дан вы
about and again we died
насчет и снова нам же померла
97 deadlines in access an important view of scarlet I
97 сроки в доступа важный вид алый я
want to choke on your hair by looking at his
хочу на волосы ты на ось ему подавиться
axis name but there PMR
заглянув назови но там пмр
Gorbachev helped Krylov and
горбачева помогла крылова и вызова на
calling Zhirinovsky so  according to mayor kravchuk it was
дом жириновский так по мэр кравчук было
honestly sprats starlings where and than 20 plates
честно кильки скворцы где и чем 20 плиты
goes a huge number of loops and the
уходит огромное количество петель и
twentieth century goes away what does this
двадцатого столетия уходит что это
mean it means that the era of the ear  dit
означает это означает что эпоха уходит
completely care go people get up stories
полностью уход идти люди встают истории
just in pairs and
просто по парам и в
let's say a
скажем
system of hysterical and hihus downed
систему истеричных и хихус сбитых так
so whims of currency on the step of Krylov and this bald one
вот блажи валюты на шаг крылова и лысого
on bachiled there another color fault
этого на бачила там другую цветовую вину
on let's say the
на скажем
president of the United States I don't know from which ones
так президенте сша не знаю из каких же
bachiled on the wildest and more
бачила на самому дикой и больше
it turns out
получается
today she has seen God's soul to lebanon and
сегодня она видала богу душу до ливана и
there beats beer and they will forget to get it, yes they will be in the
там beats пиво и забудут добуду да будут
course of the takis of the lsr ceremony, then love at the
ходу тэкис церемонии лср то любви на
sight of a number from the depths leaves an era.  only
виде числа с глубины уходит эпоха . лишь
that era gets slurped by their children, which
та эпоха забирается хлебает их дети это
means the owners until in the light, whether you
значит собственники до в свете будь ты
become unchanged and
станешь неизменным и
growth under the Russian empire, so
рост под российской империи так
1s from their such end hands,
1с с их таких ты конечных руки
especially for everyone who listens to us from
специально для всех кто нас слушает из
Russia before the collapse of the Russian empire, and that
россии до развал российской империи и то
is, these tectonic movements are also
есть тоже эти тектонические движения
British  the empire after the second world
британская империя после второй мировой
war
войны
collapsed the Austro-Hungarian empire after the first
распалась австро-венгерская после первой
world and the Russian empire after the
мировой и российской империи после
first world collapsed then until
первой мировой распалась потом до
the Soviet Union was formed and then
образовалась советский союз а потом
collapsed in 91 and now continues to disintegrate
распался в 91 и сейчас продолжает распад
because the logic of the
потому что логика
20th 21st century until what nations gain because of the
20 21 века до что наций обретают из-за
strong
сильно
Great Britain was India  so the pendant
великобритании была индия так и кулоне
did nothing britain and heard and india at once
ничего британия и слышала и индия за раз
called one power and
назвал одна держава и
alla russia russia and here you are on narumi and
алла россия россия и вот вы на наруми и
now britain
вот британия
britain saw colony and he call
британия видала colony and he называть
ok there india usa there a lot of everything was
окей там индия сша там куча всего было
that britain became poor and ukraine
что британия стала бедны и украины
gave britain all these  the colony is necessary and as a
британии отдав все эти колонии надо и в
result not to gain independence,
результате не получить независимость
Britain still remains one of the
британия все равно остается одним из
attractions  Boiling regions of the planet,
привлекательных регионов планеты
pretexts go all because it’s cool
предлоги едут все потому что там круто
there grandmothers there the development of culture and so
там бабки там развитие культуры и так
on, and russia russia is a prison and
далее а россия россия это к тюрьма и
ditches putin not releasing anyone not
канав путин не выпуская никого не
releasing anyone for that
выпуская никого за то
we are their Ust-Kan stable, then over and over the
мы их усть-кан стабильных то над так и
robot no one wants them  and you are in russia i’m
роботом никто не хочет их и ты в русе я
in bacha all there england type lyokha as if in
на бача все там англии тип лёха будто в
moscow calm down visas are issued to
москве уймитесь визы оформляются
this logic such still the russian
этому логика такая еще российская
empire maya pastors utensils not
империя майя пасторы утвари не
monoid eats them deceived numbers
моноида ест их обманула чисел алло алло
hello hello i 10
10 якуна
yakuna we need to send something from pepper with what
нам треба пришлю чего-то c перца с чему
else is there  so just like I say,
там еще так само як я скажу
try the system is collapsing so in the buda
стараетесь система рушится так в на буда
buda alignment, so there will be problems on your
буда створе вот и проблемы на своей
territory and those
территории будуте и тесь конфликты
internal conflicts there and the sunny alai oli
внутренней там и солнечный alai oli
dense unique hides and they sho whoever
плотный уник прячет а их шо хто хоче
you want Peter i mate donat you can axis
петр i mate донатом можно ось
but such address zaki dates and  that
но такие адресу заки даты и что старого
you don’t like the old one, but here we are going to thicken into the topic
не любишь его но тут у сгущаться в тему
right in the action style, so
прямо в стиле экшен направлялись так
let’s read yours, and let all the
давайте почитаем ваши , и все копья
power spears into the chatak grow up, it didn’t
питания допустить в чатак выращивали не
prove to connect faces and sponsors
доказало подключит лица и спонсорство
we won’t disassemble the super chat
супер чат таки не будем участку
and the scenes on the weekend I’ll also connect damask steel,
разобрать и сцен на выходных подключу
and so Alexa writes everything
также булат и так алекса пишет все
correctly roulette will be interesting after the
правильно рулетка будет интересно после
liberation of Kherson, we want to prove nothing,
освобождения херсона хотим ничего не
they already write that this asset,
докажешь они уже пишет что этот актив
yes, I’m checking this cycle, I’m crumpled injections of
да я чекаю циклом этим я помятой уколы
cisco all of you there referendums  already on
cisco всю вас там референдумы уже 11
September 11,
сентября
without a shave, the pilot will already make a
небритября пилотом короче уже наведет
noise in Russia’s composition, what’s more, with theirs, a bread maker of
состав россии шум еще что с ихними
amide
хлебальник амида
butter is enough for a slot, we cut
масла достаточно на слот отсекаем
off, we cut off some kind of kwan, and the bellies of
отсекаем яких я кван и будут животы
snot will talk about a gesture of goodwill
сопли рассказывать про жест доброй воли
from under the balakley, and so on,
из-под балаклеи и так далее
so our army is 1 mile from us the truth
так наша армия 1 миле до нас правдину
alla doesn’t last and everything is a brother and
алла длится не и все брат и по
technically we are still a brother and vitime lipsticks
техническому еще мы брат и помады витиме
so she is their fellow technically
так она их собрата по техническому
marked by a technologically known day you
означен по технологичному день известный
hang out such Americans and access
зависаешь такие американцы и доступ
can be seen it’s not technologically escorted
видно это не технологичным провожают
this
этом еще
poker scoop shoved all of the 19th century so
покер совок пихнул всех 19 столетия так
America developed already in the 20th  steam noise and a
америка развивалась уже в 20 пар шум и
small hut we have a calculator it
колыбу маленький у нас калькулятор это
was a curiosity and in the world also
было диковинка а в мире также
personal computers  computers were both
персональные компьютеры было обеим
so
так
read everything andreika bismarck write that
читай все андрейка бисмарк пишите что
there is a tsar so she wore tasha putin yes on
там царь так she wore таша путин да вкл
and putin bah I won’t forget
и путин бах не забуду
everything but we will be on top otherwise I think there is
все но мы будем сверху а то я думаю тут
movement on the street it was the days of
движухи таки на ул это были дни
the world football championship in the role of
чемпионат мира по футболу в роли
just a vanka  shipkov andrey's e-mail,
c просто ванькой шипкова е-мэйл андрея
please, take it to sew in, and
дайте пожалуйста возьмите на пришить в а
just tear it, write a comment on telegram
просто рвать напишите в телеграме
[ __ ] my son is tall in the body, a
коммент [__] мой сын ростом в теле
frame of
рамочку
the same robots diab &amp; vitaliy and
такой же роботы diab &amp; виталий и
just tear up throw a link in the chat models are
просто рвань кидай ссылку в чат модели
cleaning now nobody from fashion animation on
чистят сейчас никого из моды анимация на
plan antispam bot dough  so the Ottoman
плана антиспам бот тесто так османская
Empire also mined before the collapse of the
империя добыла тоже до развалилась
Russian empire, we mutated the bodies in the
российской империи мы тела мутировала в
USSR
ссср
, then Khmelnitsky, you know the history again,
то-то хмельницкий знаешь историю снова
I place people’s deputies to Magnitsky, so I
места я нардепов магнитскому так-то я 80
ask rock 40 others, I live here, of
прошу року 40 других я тут живут у
course, I know the history
конечно я знаю историю
,
так
and so Yegorka writes correctly so that more
и вот егорка пишет правильно чтоб более
that these countries are in those good relations
того эти страны в тех хороших отношениях
britain but these countries there the
британии а вот эти страны там
british commonwealth
британского содружества
private take off tying fish fish you
частному взлети обовязково рыбы рыбы ты
pendant them in private sweet in the room  well,
кулоне им в частный sweet в комнате ну и
only freedom of creativity people
только свобода творчества люди
develops hears so you take a fang a
развивается слышит так ты клык берёшь
slave and beat him with a whip inna will be
раба и бьешь его плеткой инна будет
turned away from and will not be dug effectively
отвратил от и эффективно не будет вырыта
gives freedom
нас с у частность вид дает свободу
if you want to go against work if
хочешь иди против на работу хочешь
you want to light it up on the contrary you want to be a private
напротив зажгли хочешь будет приватным
enterprise you want to create 6 and
предприятием хочешь творить 6 и
russia I'm like this totalitarian soul want
россия я вот так тоталитарно душа want
me freedom step about your pecking means
me свобода шаг про ваши клеваться значит
after earlier on the foundations of absolutism
после ранее на устои будь абсолютизма
so we have everything why the orcs are so
так что у нас все почему орки такие
sour something
кислые что-то
grow missed swam soup when it
расти пропустила плавали супа когда
gives them the same as an ear and david cola from the
придаст им же как ухо и дэвид колы с
knee insert a view of r over romashov ku ku
колена вставьте вид р над ромашов ку ку
ha rode with us three husband left and they have
ха ехала у нас три муж уехал а у них
just such a method of the public so
прямо вот я такой метод публика так
take the alleged body in chat roulette for
возьми вот якоба тела в чат-рулетке на
cheaper came true  skips and in short
дешевле сбывалось пропускает и короче
it means not to choke on their freaks in
это значит не подавиться на их чудики в
yak liquor on patients would be so screw
як ликер на пациентами бы так винтом
I will tell you some fairy tales and I
буду вам некий сказки рассказывают и я
am glad this charade in the movie d  and what did you
рад этому шарада в кино да о чем вы
decide that you are full of,
решила что вы на полон
it would be the simplest David, but
это де простейший бы давид но зато есть
yes, then your people are navkolo and love
да то ваши люди вается навколо и любят
from the brigades and the internal spoke of created a
из бригад и внутренней spoke of создал
beer ass there, we still don’t
жопу пивную там еще мы по вы не
mold you and navkolo again I’ll calm you
формовать и навколо снова чуть успокою
down a little separately and happiness  so our people
по отдельности и счастья так наши люди
deftly have mine be happy we are there
ловко у нас моих будьте счастливы мы там
still there until the future glory there insert
еще там до будущей славе там вставить
doubles in good on film so it’s
двоится в хорошему на пленку так так то
possible and the son and further against you fought and
можно и сын и дальше противо ты воевал и
then and there the abyss of vira where there is a
тогда а там бездны вира там где бывает
leg you tell me growth trends and in  russian
нога ты мне тенденции роста и в russian
words in russian
words in russian
for 1 floor attacked the
за 1 пол напал на
oak, but these ones,
дуб а вот эти так
give two daily Lenin ones, we’re just
дайте два дневных ленинскими мы просто
chic, I’m on the screensaver of
шик я вот на заставке
David, so on the screensaver of today’s
давида так на заставке сегодняшний
David of the Russian temple, then
давида российского виска тогда вин
removing the wines + their then bachyly tse vidos
снимая поставка + их то бачылы цэ видос
there sofas, you pass through the pontoon
там диваны проезжаете через понтонную
ferry, dump  death and such here
переправу сваливайте кончины и такие вот
we drive up carries God save and save
мы подъезжаем возит боже спаси и сохрани
God save and save like
боже спаси и сохрани типа
this to you even
такой вам даже
she is
она
ahead of the
опережает
freeze frame
стоп-кадр
even important I oh our God and to help
даже важно я о боже наш и на в помощь
his leg to the world and throw off  those positive
его нога миру и скиньте позитивных
memes are healthy expenses, so
мемчики здравый расходы так и
in the morning it’s aesthetic on a chair, he and it’s
вы утром это эстетическую на стул он и
important, there we’ll already be a minibus
це дуже важливо там уже будем маршрутчик
waitress in caviar, not so, that is, at the
официантка в caviar не так то есть на
factory, the daughter’s clip is disgusting, but he and
заводе там противны клипса дочку же он и
they need HIV from you straight hanging because
им потребно вич у тя прямой висящую ведь
it happens behind on what  our karina collapse
бывает позади на чём наша карина рухайся
so I’m growing it already even the house and teshina after
так ращу это уже даже дом и цешина ведь
all, the langley donation didn’t come
не пришел лэнгли
all at home no, I think it’s cmm
дарственную все дома нет я думаю это cmm
I won’t be viral graying this mouse and there
не буду вирусным седов эту мышь и
will be new and new calla memes to blame
будут и виноватых новый и новый мемы
so the Russians will be oleg memchik
чудить так россиян и будет олегом мемчик
cool facial expressions the actor of whom the peasant with the
прикольно мимика актер кого мужика с
text is just cool then the negative
текстом просто классно то отрицательное
offensive olga capricorn i will benefit andrey belarus belarus
наступлением ольга козерог я выгадает
attack us it
андрей беларуси беларуси нападают на нас
was read never to find the key and palyha
читалось никогда не найти ключа и палиха
to
к
49 tsyba i am a belarusian so I knocked out a russian
49 цыба я белорус так вот выбил русский
disk so I mean 24  fiercely to
дисковый так я же разумеет 24 люто вам к
you before the order of the
вам бы до наказ
father,
батька
this kind of delay to slap
этот вид delay надавать
ukraine so stir up carmichael and
украине так разворошит carmichael и
no one should you
никто не надо ли вы стоит
appear in  we are Belarusian at the same time, ambushes
появиться вы белорус за раз таки засады
in this and from now on
в это и отныне
[laughter]
[смех]
fought and the
воевали и
withdrawal of Belarus and allegedly thinks
вывод беларусь и якобы думает
I show to achieve and so bill Russian
я проявляю достигать и так билл русские
generals
генералы
and
и
xa to reset the forces of Ukraine the infection to prepare
xa сбросить силы украины зараза готовить
such everywhere lei give effective grow
таких везде лей давать эффективных расти
so moreover, in
так причем на
prepared to grow and positions I
подготовленных расти и позициях
just take  it’s worth poking in here the
просто беру стоит сунуться сюда
water just let’s say
вода просто скажем
he didn’t survive the carnival I think only about the
карнавал ему не пережила я думаю лишь о
territory of Belarus jenny and who in the
территории беларуси дженни а кого в
tornan was recognized by Belarus there will be
торнане признали белоруссии буду
scarlet dirty tricks and a brush maybe pipes you look like a
алая пакости и кисть может трубы ты вид
roll you wow and there were boilers you can
вали-ка ты вов и быть были котлы можете
absolutely right since you wine is the rate of
абсолютно верно так как вы вино ставкой
tragedy  how can wine be worth the Volyn
трагедии як можна вино стоит волынской
tragedy, so the power that ce bulo
трагедии так власть которая це було
between book jokes is further
между книжными шуточками дальнейшем
captivating to the Poles and someone where the
пленительные полякам и а кто-то там где
bull and
bull и
problems I go to the Ukrainian side so
проблемы я к украинской стороны так
using it you can return, that is,
используя можно вернуться то есть делает
does not waste anything, I’m a lumbar triune,
ничего не тратить я поясничная троедина
so the words were sewn up by dad for dancing  I read it,
так слова зашил папа для танцев же читал
but why orcs sewing the firstfruits scrolled
но почему орки шитье начаток прокрутился
hoo gouging is written in one about lobster
ого раздолбай пишется в одно про омара
where they have a microwave  and in apartments for 10
куда у них микроволновки в квартирах 10
years they were up to trampling and we had bags [ __ ]
годах были до топтал и у нас кулёчки бля
promised and nice when unpacking soap
обещал и милы при распасовку мыло
bags and hung them so that we could stew on
кулёчки и вешала чтобы у нас тушилось на
this husband and we had such activists and the
эту муж а у нас такие к активисты был и
future and there are already bags in you hannah
будущее а там уже кулёчки в ты ханны
bulla and someone  still a sack of string bags
буллу а кто-то еще торба таки авоськи
bull and
bull и
death is not shorter for and for the fact that the church was
гибель не короче на и за то что церковь
what a sack was, but if it’s so
какой торба было а если то чтобы как
moronic how much was the release of
дебильного сколько было выпуску этикеток
labels basically tight so the referendum in the
в основном плотно так референдум
bryansk region of the Belgorod region is not already
брянщине белгородчине курсе не уже
another mobile you are not up to
другое мобилы ты не до
ismail blackmail andrey if you are reading this
исмаил шантаж андрей если ты это читаешь
so that Zhiganov’s health is trouble for this
чтобы за это беду жиганова здоровье
ismail khan thank you write ismail which country you are from
исмаил хан спасибо напиши исмаил ты с
because I remember that
какой страны потому что я помню что ты
you sometimes try
и русскоязычной так иногда пробуешь
to sign Ukrainian and in Ukrainian and
подписать украинский и по-украински и
translate this, write where exactly you
это переводишь напиши откуда именно ты
are from who you are by nationality, it’s interesting
кто ты по национальности интересно
in this and now Alaska so  the forces began the
в этом и сейчас аляску так силы начали
culture of belarus already talked and
культуры беларуси уже поговорил и
hello from the crimea crimea thermite with on
здравствуйте с крыма крым thermite с на
and cram the military facility to the crimea there
и напихать туда войсковых объекте крыму
I showed the zilairsky further to the necessary yesterday to
я казав зилаирский далее до нужной вчера
fool belg
дурачить белграде чужой
instead of a stranger, the electrical substation was depressed, so instead of it it was a
электроподстанция так и пи вместо было
base with lace up quote there, I ran
base with lace up цитата там бахнуло
all the clap and a flash of light, and
бегу все хлопок и световая вспышка а
then the body,
потом теле
so I will call it if all there are exits of
так я назову если все будут выходы
Scotland from Britain, I believe that I filmed
шотландии из британии верится что заснял
for medical reason twitter on the
по лечебно причина twitter на рахунок
Scottish rahunok and up to the site smoothly  the topic for
шотландии так и до сайт складно тема для
us, let’s say inside, will only bring the Scots to reason,
нас скажем внутрь образумит лишь
so the plankita are the beginnings of the
шотландцы так что планкита начатки
Celtic plan, so the very Irish and
кельтских плана так так самые ирландцы а
England tsetse the beginnings of the Germanic tribes, and
англии цеце начатки германских племен и
even after the fall of the Roman Empire, they
и после падения римской империи до
came to the British streams and pressed against
пришли на британские струи и потеснил с
them, well, in principle, the Scottish people
их ну в принципе у шотландского народа
black from
black от
h &amp; m
h&amp;m
let’s say the truth  it shouldn’t be
скажем правда не должен быть она и
humidity either, so it’s just like Ukraine got the
влажности так само як украина добывала
chair dark to call it so well, I think that
стуле темно называть так ну я думаю что
we are there by name a Cossack about not Scotland
мы по имени там казак о не шотландии
to go around means there Russia is going where I
чтобы ходится значит там руси еду куда я
hand it’s clear that Russia playing samples
руку ясно что россия играя пробы
joyfully wipe everyone chihu light so
радостно всех протри чиху свете так
Alaric show
аларик шоу
people  scotland this overbearing scotland
народ шотландии этот властный шотландии
on those wanto you call us like that it's
на те хочемо ты называешь нас так то
normal and already like that and I think again
нормально и уже так и я думаю еще
let's say
скажем
now  as he will also
сейчас он так же
be this, in principle, an hour private
будет этом еще в принципе часу частный
sweet dismantles the azov-city to the lower
sweet разбирает азов-сити низшему
strain the same European Union, as it were,
напрягать той самой евросоюз как бы там
they tell me, but I am the national powers,
на рассказывают а я национальные державы
alla, the food is rich in the process, we are
алла еду же богата процессе нам
national, so the currency, I will say
национальным же так валюта я скажу
Mikeshin is rarely evil on and then but holy
микешин редко зло на и тогда но свят
holy and they will give you a vegetable forgive me that's why
свят и дадут овощем простишь вот почему
earlier so there then lessons in that 200 bulo
раньше так там то уроки в том 200 було
it was accepted man was the right
это было принято мужик был правильный
transport for rent to you than de stat from the
транспорт напрокат вам чем de stat из
UK you needed bulo tests them
великобритании вам треба було тестами их
and you finally transplanted a month so you can
а ты наконец пересадками месяц так можно
then pleased otherwise you can grow in it then you
потом pleased иначе в ней тогда зарасти
can  forgotten perlite for he is against so that
можно забытый перлит за он против дабы
you come to the airport and come there
вы приехали в аэропорт приехал и там
quickly so access and to others
быстро так доступ и к другим
came the doctrine of fiery information
пришли учение огненную информации
quickly was kind of edit and the club so the
быстрого было вид править и клуба так
wallpaper of Kostikov's freak on a horse and quietly no
обои костикова чудика на коне и тихо нет
skakovskaya with a machine gun you wait
скаковская с автоматом ты ждать для того
for Mrs. there to where  there is a board
чтобы миссис там чтобы куда есть доска
cats bearded departure of kindness engine then
коты бородатый выезд доброты engine то
for 1 both for information and up to a
за 1 обе на информацию и до
second and so the rest itself capital sharks
секунды и так сама отдых капитал акулы
tremble at us sun  duk it was just at a
дрожь кидает у нас сундук было просто за
time I pressed the switching button
раз я нажала кнопочку коммутирующих
came to go the process and send the exchange so
пришли идти процесс и пришлите обмен так
in the retinue of this let's say for the people of the neck of our
в свите этому скажем для людей шеи наших
brothers
братьев
people and china live abroad six
люди и китай за кордоном живут шесть
bottles of other lyudmila in our
бутылок иных людмила у нашего же
generation so you interfered with the generation of our
поколения так ты мешал поколения наших
children and will be so people on  ordering a cordon, the
детей и будут так люди на заказа кордону
church is such a belda in the neighboring
церковь такая самая бельды на соседней
region, well, boccia a bunch of times the Poles there are a
области ну boccia кучу раз поляки там
bunch of non-fluid result dc vn from 2 and
куча не текучий результате dc вн из 2 и
you’re completely perceiving these
ты совсем причем воспринимая эти
processes and I had to pass the DAC
процессы и мне пришлось не прошедшие цап
so Crimea then Ukraine matt dada to the
так крым то украина мэтт дока папы к
song spoke to the main
песне spoke to главная расскажите
please tell  about the history of the red-black
пожалуйста про историю красно-черного
flag, see the red-black flag is the
флага смотрите красно-черный флаг это
flag of the organization of Ukrainian
флаг организации украинских
nationalists, the fact is
дело в том что
that it symbolized them, you need to say
что он них символизировал нужно сказать
so they chose such colors
так вот они выбрали такое такие цвета
under this flag, they fought for the
под этим флагом боролись за
independence of Ukraine, the Ukrainian
независимость украины украинская
insurgent army,
повстанческая армия
this flag is also considered
этот флаг тоже считается украинского
the flag of the Ukrainian people
народа флагом
national liberation struggle
национально-освободительной борьбы
and some such let's say why
а какого то такого скажем почему вот
it was red black took no they gave
именно красный черные взяли нет дали
such a flag to themselves so and cons so you
такой флаг себе так и минусы так ты
came
пришел
were countries garand this is an action trouble pawns of
были страны garand это акция беда пешки
corners
углов
maria kovalchuk writes a military tragedy
мария ковальчук пишет воинская трагедия
not everything is so unambiguous it is
не все так однозначно мне здесь
told to me here in moscow often
рассказывается в москве часто
practiced aggregates about the days of life their warriors
практиковал агрегаты о днях быт их воины
upa on twitter we are right  let's talk
упа на twitter нас правой давайте
about you in Ukrainian and Polish speeches on
про ты речами украинским и польским на
doubting the technical territories of the
сомневаться техничных территориях блок
block and in the twentieth cut off the bogota doblo
так и в двадцатом отпилите боготу doblo
rhythmic krutari strain i.e.  placement of the
ритмичных крутари штамм т.е. размещение
territory for rent here I technically honor the
территории напрокат вот я технично чести
territory and the excess salad Ukrainian
территории а излишняя салатом украинские
villages Polish so lettuce Serbian villages
села польский так салатом сербские села
Croatian and so on and so forth there may
хорват и так дальше так там завжды может
be ethnic features and at the moment cool and the
будто этнические черты и в момент cool и
mace is a military period there the ideal of the
булаву это военный периода там идеала
army of the kraiova
армия крайова
search for such from dawn should not be the
поиска таких от осенило не должны
right speech  and the Ukrainian rebels the
правильные речи и украински повстанцы
crew on the task of nail and correct
экипаж на задаче nail и правильные
before so c-block qualitatively
раньше так c-block качественно истории
mercury stories and I will take out from their Ukrainians what the
ртутным а я выну от их украинцев че
guilty Poles of history are the table to god bull
виноватых поляки истории стол богу bull
and the
и
yaki people
люди яки
say channel and
скажем channel и
wrong hello it will be all that
неправильно алло это будешь весь кого
kind of star was a problem 23 at a time not  in
этакий star была проблема 23 за раз не в
ukraine shadows palliative may i kremiki
украине тени паллиативный мая я кремики
has marina lee ki hai mutual
has marina lee ki hai взаимных
claims ding-don-da we have rented and
претензиях дин-дон-да у нас е напрокат и
technical territories kiza lost in poland
техничные территории киза лишилась на
there home plague
территории польши там home чума
there is personal territory those hear
есть личный территории те слышать на
scarlet slovaks on the pavement otherwise we are
тротуаре словачек алым иное мы
engaged in this revisionism to from
занимаемся этим ревизионизмом до от
islands will come for slaves for a brother from Poland
рабов придут острова за брата у польши
hall hiding a man well, we don’t hide
холл мужчину прячущий ну так не прячем
17 Slovak women  so
17 словачек так
hot and russia so in russia that's their
горяч и россия так в россии вот их что
brother and the
брат и
execution of polish polish officers
расстрел польскую польских офицеров
vegan vlada katyn.  a ticket,
веганскую владу катынь . тикет
yes, it’s visible for the 1st,
да вот видимом за 1
I lived to read it, and
го жил его почитать и
here I am Katyn growth on or the Katyn
вот я катынский рост на или катынский
execution,
расстрел
especially let someone watch us from
особенно давайте кто нас смотрит из
Russia or Russian-speaking countries in
россии как или русскоязычных стран в
Soviet historiography there is such a hut
советской историографии есть такая хаты
that the
что фашисты
Nazis burned the village to the best of Russia, so that is, huts
немцы сожгли деревню так то есть хаты
as in forty  in the third year and
как в сорок третьем году и
Soviet propaganda, now you
советская пропаганда вот вы сейчас
see how Russian propaganda works,
видите как работает российская
what skills they
пропаганда какие навыки генерируют так
generate from scratch, and when there is a
на пустом месте и при том когда есть
lot of evidence that this was not so in
куча подтверждений что это было не так в
Soviet propaganda, it was easier
советской пропаганды у нее было проще
for people as people did not have videos so to
как у людей не было видосиков так чтобы
show and now  in the forty-third year before, the
показать и вот в сорок третьем году до
Shakhty tragedy is attributed so
приписывается шахтинская трагедии так
that the
что
Germans burned the whole village, and why exactly the
немцы сожгли целого село а почему именно
huts,
хаты
and if we see everything, there was the village of Katyn in the
а если мы видим все было село катынь еще
forty-first year, as in the forty-first
сорок первом году как в сорок первом
year, the Soviet troops were
году советские войска
not Yanka troops, the summer resident was not even at 40, not
не войска янка вы дачник даже не в 40 не
earlier, not 41
раньше не 41
up to the sleeve of the
до с рукава
fortieth year, so
сороковом году так
the Soviet NKVD shot
нквд советская расстреляла
Polish officers, let's see, or
польских офицеров давайте посмотрим или
in Russian Wikipedia there is this
в русской википедии есть это
yes, the Katyn
да катынский расстрел на
execution, let’s speak in Russian specifically about the
вот давайте по-русски специально про
strain so that the people of their Russia understand it so
штамм чтобы люди их россии поняли так
that everyone who is talking about this advice is kissel until the
все которые вот про этот совет кисиль до
fortieth year of the cancer year, it’s still Hitler
сороковой год раковый год это еще гитлер
didn’t attack the Soviet Union, the
не напал на советский союз
Great Patriotic War didn’t start like that,
великая отечественная война не начал так
but the Soviet state
но советское государство
carried out at home  on the territory of the
осуществляло у себя на территории
massacres of Polish citizens in
массовые убийства польских граждан в
one of the captured officers of the Polish army
одном пленных офицеров польской армии
which captured officers of the Polish army in the
какие пленные офицеры польской армии в
fortieth year the Soviet Union had and
сороковом году были у советского союза и
we understand simply from in Russia at school and
мы понимаем просто от в россии в школе и
it doesn’t even pass that in the thirty-ninth
даже не проходит что в тридцать девятом
year before the Soviet Union
году до советский союз с нацистской
concluded a pact with Nazi Germany
германии заключил пакт
Molotov-Ribbentrop on the division of spheres and the
молотова-риббентропа о разделе сфер и
Second World War began because
вторая мировая война началась того что
Hitler from the environment and the union essentially tore
гитлер из сред и союз по сути разорвали
Poland into 2 parts, so by their unsuccessful
польшу на 2 часть так по своей неудачной
agreement, and it turns out when the
договоренности и получается когда
Soviet Swift came out to inflate part of
советский свифт вышел надуть часть
Poland, Hitler on another, they themselves carried out
польши гитлер на другую они себе провели
such a water division of Poland and
такой вода раздел польши и
Polish officers, they were captured by the
польских офицеров они были в плену у
Soviet Union in the fortieth year then
советского союза в сороковом году то
the Soviet Union
советский союз
started World War II together with Hitler
начал вместе с гитлером вторую мировую
and
войну и
in order to later hide this one,
для того чтобы потом скрыть вот этот
let's say
скажем
informationally interrupt this
информационно перебить вот этот
Katyn execution, so rare propaganda is
катынский расстрел так редкая пропаганда
just like that there are cats you need to make a
дело просто так есть коты надо сделать
move and and from and everywhere then dragged
ход и и вот от и и всюду таскались потом
from one hut new Katyn for  why, in
с одной хаты new катынью для чего для
order to informationally interrupt
того чтобы информационно перебить вот
these cats, how because when a person
это коты как потому что когда человек
thinks if in the 40th year he also
думает если в 40 ом году так еще и
starts to think something, the Katyn
начинает думать что-то катынский
execution, and somehow in the fortieth year, the
расстрел да как-то в сороковом году
Soviet Union before shot Polish
советский союз до расстреливал польских
captured officers if the Soviet Union
пленных офицеров если советский союз
only began to fight  in the forty-first,
начал воевать только в сорок первом
put plus Che you before the plague about the
поставьте плюс че вы раньше чумы про
Katyn massacre, here is their radian
катынский расстрел вот их радианс ким
union of Polish semi-us and put a
союзом польских полу нами и поставьте
minus yes, if you hear about such a Katyn massacre for the first time,
минус да если вы впервые слышите про
also in evil, well, Russian propaganda
также во зло ну российская пропаганда
wanna against and Bashneft, we
wanna против и башнефти мы фейками этому
even raised it correctly with fakes and potal  it is necessary about the
даже правильно поднял и поталь надо про
fact that when he changed clothes under the
то что он когда переодевалась под
gaze of the hetman of the rebels channel and
взглядом к гетману повстанцев channel и
most of the  I would also reduce the
большинства для то еще бы уменьшите
special pit market by the population of the
специальным пит рынку населением
rebels
повстанцев
so
так
I’m circling this number was 75 defense
я кружусь это число было 75 защиту
of the non-nuclear cross from an eyebrow brick from a
креста не ядерного из брови кирпич от
friend the holy manager was the United States that
друга святой менеджер было сша что
Hiroshima was on gas from the
хиросимы на газ от
wind even before Hiroshima and Nagasaki it’s not
ветер еще до хиросимы и нагасаки тут не
so often that Japan was the
таки частому что там япония была
aggressor there  so Sashan was destroyed
агрессором так а сашан и была разрушена
here absolutely Russia defended itself and
защищалась тут абсолютно так россия и а
if so then Ukraine banged across
раз так то это украина бабахнуло по
Russia it would be nice right away so Russia
россии это было бы сразу мило так россия
tell me what reached the mouth of this
скажи мне что за достиг устья данного
strike at Pliny I think I will
удара по у плиния думается буду
stay a multiple in the international will be
останемся кратный в международном будут
exactly etc.  .  international outcast russia
точно т.д. международный изгой россия
i think yes and the price is trouble so
думаю да и цена беда так
hello andreya yourself chair tell me
здравствуйте андрея сами стул подскажите
your attitude to set galicia if you
свое отношение к сет галичина если вы
were from sum so you would
были из сум так вы бы снова галиб china
not write again galib china like galicia
не писали как галичина
you are not from the bag
вы же не из сумки чины правда и так
that is, above the
то есть выше
great holy battle kolya porsche 1500 km
великий свята битва коля porsche 1500 км
to the
до
battle pit portion I have a year to you
битва пит порцию я с году вам его
in one of his mind yes fool here we
в одном из своему виду да дурач вот мы
have grown so glad today
выросли так рада сегодня
1514 lesson of
1514 уроком
moscow to a straight line with julya view of the foliage of the lithuanian
москвы до прямой с юлей вид листва
pen and we drive
литовского ручку и же мы диск
such power detective  Ukrainians who are
такой державы детектив украинцы кто
violating Belarus
нарушению беларуси
against Moscow, so read all the same life
против москвы так почитайте все таки быт
yells a portion then write a
вопит порцию потом писля
stream so dosvidos go to the bow and point
стрима так досвидос идти к луку и укажи
out there Russia like always won Russia
там россия типа всегда побеждало россия
with a sticker raked out and
стикером выгребал а так
just head on for waiting for a vipadka of deceptions
прямо голова на за жду випадку обманов
tandoor there mistresses and throw to you and
тандыры там любовницы и кинуть к вас и
so on  admin here is above your fer if I
так далее админ вот выше вашей фер если
wait interesting thank you admin [ __ ]
дождусь интересным благодарю админ wog
super we raise us three top 1 to dad not
супер мы поднимаем нас три топ-1 папе не
tune-auto faces with o friend top to stream and
тюн-авто лица с о друге top to stream и
attempts well t  am here series comrade
попыток ну там сюда series товарищ
stayed there three boils 1 she gets
пробыли там трожь кипень 1 она получает
depression and
депрессивность а
olga capricorn us in the year iso 51200 we
ольга козерог нам на году iso 51200
buy so jumped and the
покупаем таким прыгнул и
Ukrainian land from the good so fifty-
украинскую землю у доброго так пятьдесят
one thousand two hundred and fifty and even better
одна тысяча двести пятьдесят и дуже
that at a time in Kharkov for
добре что за раз на в харьковском на
premka I think to start the armor of strength  to
премку я думаю начать брони силы до
hot replenish the exchange fund
горячих пополнить обменный фонд
then it will be these whether you eat me on our
тогда будет этих едят ли меня ты на наши
reefs and at the same time is in the dungeons of the
рифы и за раз находится в застенках
Putin regime
путинского режима
so
так
you know such psych channels I don’t know
знаете такие каналы psych не знаю
blueberries or at the very bottom of the Ukrainian
чернику или в самом низу украинскую
land
землю от червонный роб правоту за
interpretations of us really poke
частной интерпретации нас правде тыкаюсь
oolong itself,
улун сама
let's say I meet us in the format of dasha oolong
скажем я нас встречают формате даша улун
club c and about parkour and primala itself such an
club c и про паркур и примала сама такой
interpretation
интерпретации
would like to be afraid of the brethren with the sich
хотел бы побоишься около братию с
blogger where tomorrow vader
блогером сечей куда вот завтра вейдер
backs video with the blogger captain and there would be
спины видео с блогером капитан и бы там
giblets work work vidos with roman
потрошки работы работы видосы с римским
Fortunately, I think there someone has on
благом думаю там у кого-то есть на
topical topics to try to Alexander
актуальные темы пробовать до александр
Sidorenko in the media, I'm still the same g  alichina
сидоренко по сми я все та же галичина
when a guy from in Russian
когда парень из на русском языке
asks about s from galicia this is
спрашивает про с с галичина это
so I who respects very much / russia as well as
так я кто уважает очень / россия а также
bulo andrey the Katyn execution should also be mentioned
андрей также следует упомянуть катынский
, but here we are already a man of special
расстрел а вот мы уже да мужик особого
reason
резона
in the face to the nightingales skin of the Dutchman is also a
по морде до соловьев скин голландца тоже
cool topic I don’t know what he is  there the
прикольная тема не знаю что ему там
statutes of alive are fun and fun,
уставов alive весело-весело
so
так
you
при
know how the wood on the
знаешь как древесина на
arti for which he reached Berlin what
арти за на который дошел до берлина как
is the name of this dude inside, in
зовут внутрь
short, a quilted jacket so his
этот чувак короче [__] так у него так
hat with earflaps burns so painlessly, then
горит шапка-ушанка так беспалевно то
at first he asked the process of galib what and
сначала спросил процесс галиб чему а
now he says that the feat of the Sumy
теперь говорит что подвиг сумского
partisan who  reached berlin, what is
партизана который дошел до берлина как
his name,
его зовут
partisans don’t go on the attack in short,
партизаны не ходят в атаку короче куда
somewhere in a neighboring country, so partisans
то в соседнюю страну так партизаны
partisans on the ground, this is a partisan
партизанит на местности это партизанка
on a happy kind of berlin
на хэппи рода берлин
shooting by boys
расстрел мальчиками
where to watch a video about under anton in the
где посмотреть видео про под антон в
telegram channel and
telegram канала и
what time you are in the cage
вы в какое время находитесь в клетке
i don’t have  some one time and
нету у меня какого-то одного временем и
sleep happens in the morning but rarely
сном бывает первой половине дня но редко
go out there example I will help you go out a week a couple of times
выхожу там пример помогу неделю пару раз
take off now very little time
выйти снять сейчас очень мало времени
has passed with my work
прошло с моей работой
activities are very busy these weeks
деятельностью занят сильно в эти недели
so but slash week we will determine more
так но слэш неделю определим больше
attention in modeling
внимания в лепке
so you can earn a stream with a belarusian
так можно заработать стрим с белорусом
you can be
можно суровым так про канал бог
harsh  food minutes and from sawing a
дайте питания minutes а из распилить
video and costa not a book you read to
видосик и коста не книжку вы прочитать к
I haven’t read a circle for a long time someone I’ll
я давно не читал кружок кто-то я
say an artist at the explosion that people
скажем художник при взрыве что народ
class blaze so andrei attempts daddy you
классу блейз так андрей попытки папик ты
respect ukraine so baby brahman is shorter
уважаешь украины так baby браман короче
and giving the jar the width of the dog pix small
и дав банку ширина пса по пикс маленькой
and  ukraine with a little shorter this is my
и украина с маленькой короче это мои
teeth an hour he again hyip teach me the result
зубы час он опять hyip учить я результат
from and domains and before my state
из и домены и до моей державы
benefit rzhaka that I am from moss ha ha
benefit ржака в том что я из мха ха ха
it is that you don’t you bathe that we have
это что вы не вы купаетесь что у нас по
99 percent burning load of penny jack I
99 процентов горит нагрузка пенни джек я
was in  minds and more than once, I know that there is,
был в умах и не раз так я знаю что там
and so, but where there is no Bella, that
ну и так но там где белла в каких нет то
is, there are more educated people, like I
есть там люди более образованные как я
don’t know a person who is from Sumy who
не знаю человек который из сум который
heard the Ukrainian language  more than once in the news I
слышал украинский язык не раз в новостях
saw on msi never dump personally
видел на msi никогда не свалка лично
yogurt badge yogurt galicia in which
йогурт бляха йогурт галичина в каких
stores the sumchanin is sold if you
магазинах продается сумчанин если бы ты
saw the words there and personally you are already in your
видел там слова а лично вы уже у тебя в
head ladies
голове дам
even before the calculation with Russian bloggers
еще до выкладку с российским блогерам
davidovich crap wines and so the
давидович обосрался вин и так
picture of Repin Cossacks swells  in the old man
картина репина казаки пышет в старицком
at the sultan
у султану
when the boys zara on the 5th in the banana
когда пацанчики zara на 5-ом в банан
calm down and sumchanin
успокоимся и сумчанин
so and
так и
how many languages do you know the question clips are m
сколько языков вы знаете вопрос
lting ski team of you know the food that y
клипы тает ski team of ты знаешь
u contribute this concept banner mago I know
питание что вы вклада это понятие знамя
the neck of Chinese and Japanese there called ever
mago я знаю шея китайской и японской там
where a kid that's how much  people you
назвал везде кида вот сколько людей ты
know you named how many languages you know
знаешь ты назвал сколько языков ты
ood wiki
знаешь питания
orld and on these new ones you can commu
вики мире и на этих новых ты можешь
e of someone of their fellow Ukrainian Russi
коммуне кого-то их собрата украинскую
n Yes I can lay down English I can see I
российскую да я можем вильно укладывать
read my mind by ear or there
видно читаю вильно разуме на слух али
is little practice and lively interpretation, since
мало практики и живого толкования так
then we Nikolas fall  in saratov
как то мы николы попадают в саратове
shields of grass of the postulate of syria I am the
щиты травы постулата сирийскую я
cob of troch odopt is the party
спочатку трохи одопту is the party
starting we begin to design our
начиная начинаем же конструировать свои
rooks
грачи
for the benefit of understanding  fully read
пользу разумению полностью читаю
fully
полностью
i tried in chat and chinese laws and
я пробовал в чат и китайского законов и
right so i can't say i know chinese
справа так я не скажешь я знаю китайскую
so hit and i'll give kim soo hyung
так попал и я дам ким су хён
so
так
sorry for the nitpick but ukrainian they are
простите за придирка но украинские они
ukrainian before ukrainian they are ukrainian
украинский до украинский они украинский
yes but sometimes in russian i speak
да но иногда на русском языке я говорю
incorrectly raising before  sunset and not
неправильно повышение перед закатом и не
native, I don’t know Russian well, he’s to and
родной я плохо знаю русский язык он к и
there the Russian language is distorted this
там русский язык он исковерканы этот
wrong Slavic sometimes mistakes
неправильный славянский иногда ошибки
how it is so
каким его так
hello white church
привет белой церкви
andrey good evening hello from temporarily
андрей добрый вечер привет с временно
occupied tibby is there any cool
оккупирована tibby ли какой классный
joke so stopudovo ukraine can be
прикол так стопудово украина можно
written completely in capital letters like
писать полностью большими буквами как и
rush about the thefts on purchases of weapons in the
носишься кражам на закупках оружия в
government I heard something of Vitalin I have
правительстве слышал что либо виталина я
not heard about the thefts of
не слышал про кражи
purchases of weapons in the government and you
закупок оружия в правительстве и вы
throw out such things so very similar
выкидываете такие вещи так очень похожи
to the
на
Russian just a
российскую просто
cycle
цикл
so
так
you are a programmer I'm already sick of seeing
вы программист я уже задолбавший
before the court a programmer
повидаться до суда программист
so and speak English
так и спик инглиш
go there and
зайдите туда и
drunk  I'm on, thanks to the
пьяном я на мы сильно благодаря
communists, we launched our native me  the
коммунистам запустили свой родной язык
language of my city is Dnepropetrovsk, as a basis, everyone speaks Russian only
говорят на русском языке на только
because since childhood they have been taught at home in
потому что так с детства учили дома на
their native language under the normal policy of the
родной язык на при нормальной политики
state, so for 15 10 years it will be or like
государства так лет 15 10 будет или типа
Ukrainian is normal and I think you are
украинский нормально и я думаю ты чего
going to soak the schools or the cob about
школы будет замочить или початок о самих
themselves  it’s cold, I think that it’s normal for no
же холодно я думаю что нормально никто
one to freeze until the optimization children will be
не замерзнуть до будут дети оптимизации
rented schools will be released on a remote
напрокат школы выпустят на дистанционное
start to rent to fill the decks
начали напрокат чтобы набивать деки
holding the installation, too, let
держание установа тоже пускай учусь
me learn dante for the same 1 watering the universe acad
dante для тож 1 полива the universe акад
and send it to the home chief city
и отправлять на домашний начальник city
fierce yes just where aloyan and I think
лютой да просто куда алоян и думаю еще
I will still be  there is still a direct mayor of the critical
буду еще есть прям мэра критических
cycles of that
тактов той байка
Moskalev bike, so many whispers, winter, everyone
москалев столько шёпот вот зима все
will freeze to get food, the muscle in the center
замерзнут добывать еду мышца в центре
,
так
because it just doesn’t seem to you,
ведь она лишь и не кажется для вы его
so maybe it’s real and my chair was
так может он реальный и стул у меня были
like that.  they don’t always believe me either, and it’s possible from the
такими . мне тоже не всегда верят и из
Crimea, but he’s a strong board and was
крыма возможно но он сильно борт и был
like we decided the template practiced
как мы решили шаблон потренировался
respect for people
уважению к людям
alexander nikolay little friend today
александр николай мало друга сегодня
pen pen and russia the Russian rocket
ручка ручка а россия российская ракета
hit the hut on and the doctor took kuvings because
попала в хату на и kuvings брал врач ибо
from the lessons by the minute and together the pit
от уроки по минутам и вместе яма
depth of 14 to andrey you heard about
глубиной 14 до андрей вы слышали про
wooden hammers and the dacha, I think something
деревянные hammers и дачу я думаю что то
more laman of such psychological
бильше ламан такой психологический
propaganda of ours is so right that then
пропаганды нашей так правильно что потом
already in the 2nd verse of the ruble you would think so the
уже 2 стихе рублик бы вздумай так
Russians, then how do you explain to us the
россиян то как нам все-таки объясни в
toilet is horrible and then we will already give
туалет попало и тогда мы уже на даст
entity  dadykin at a distance
entity дадыкин на дистанции андрей
andrey recognizes yuri smartly yuri veliki is a flower
вызнает юрия бойко юрий велики цветочек
parodist their sway great-grandfather tobacconists 2
пародист их шатайте прадеда табачники 2
breed
породе
so about the arms trade by our
так про торговле оружием нашим
Ukrainian government
украинским правительством
it is not visible read on the u tube of a swede
это не видно почитайте на ю тубе швеца
from the usa you will learn about the ermak the
из сша узнаете о ермаке команде
president’s team but even so
президента но и так
by 5 crankshafts of which the whole is shorter than a
на 5 коленвал коим целого короче
hindu such  it’s written like this, let’s
индуиста такими написано так вот давайте
not twitter, we won’t have to drop all
twitter не надо нам будет сбрасывать вот
this all kinds of chemistry, in short, you have a
эту всякую химию уж у вас короче там
ermak selling h  im or zelensky treasure they
ермак продает him or сокровище зеленский
still sell cartridges and so on
еще продают патроны и так дальше
some kind of fog to us therefore here katya romchik then a
какую-то к мы поэтому тут катя ромчик то
birman then louder to you and tell
бирман то громче к тебе и передай
living on the air the queen should be with
обитанием в эфире the queen надо с
such steve flutes of windows ferry from dad to
такими стив канавок винды ферри у папы к
so katya and everything bachish like  to be so
так что катя и все бачишь like to be так
loud here romka don't miss the lessons
громко тут ромка не пропускай уроки
astana on the air three attempts you are in taman
астана эфире три попытки вы в тамани
yanyk languid jumps of the throat today
янык томные прыжки горлова сегодня у нас
we hope roulette I mean I say and
мы надеемся рулетка бишь я говорю и
tell the
расскажем
disenfranchised time troshki
бесправных времени трошки
mouth her throat
уст ее горло
you know shell this friend helped about the
вы знаете shell это друга помогал о
eldar 2 loops all for the lesson  we are at the
эльдар 2 петли вся на урок мы на початку
beginning of the lesson, the reader skovchite told everyone
урока вчителька сковчите рассказал всем
Elizabeth's friend is flexible until March, and then it
гибки елизавета друга по март и тут
comes, that is, according to these records and
приходит то есть по этим записи и
how clearly there are so many viewers like a
как четко столько зрители столько like a
g6 nadym that there are
g6 надыме что там с лайками a
more likes with likes a distant likes people more today and who before
лайков человек больше сегодня да кто до
us I will not tell you about it  I’ll be roulette today,
нас про это я расскажу не буду сегодня
I would decide today the boards for
рулетки я бы решивший сегодня борта под
sawing sprats from you, we mom have access
пилку от вас кильки мы мама доступ
pot-bellied new ones in the Kharkiv region, so
пузатыми новые на харьковщине так
I need to live in the Kherson region because, that
херсонщины треба живу поскольку а то
is, Peter i mate, let’s say  we are three Ukrainians
есть петр i mate скажем нас три украинцы
petr i mate morale petr and the motive of
петр i mate боевый дух петр и мотив
foamy force the clinician survived from
пенными силу клиницисту же выжил от
helping her [ __ ] experience does not want and raised
помог ей киску опыта не хочет и поднятой
these tests to drag here in the chat and we will
эти испытания на тащи сюда в чат и будем
raise them to scald like sho the fool
их поднимать ее обваривать як шо дурачек
mines wants to transfer and the topics to friends
шахтах хочет передать и темы друзьям
beat themselves-  then the equestrian
бить сам-то и конного
front, who at a time is called a stream,
фронту кто за раз называется стрим
to convey about which of the food tekke grooves to me, I
передать о ком из пищи текке пазы мне
’ll call a huyak
хуяк назвать передам
1,400 while the
1 400 пока
lawyers, the
юристы
doctor, with Katya’s aromas, you also convey all the
врач ароматами катя тоже передаёшь и все
norms such as growth and Andrei’s on the stream
нормы типа роста и у андрея на стриме
means everything is normal for dinner and is experiencing
значит всё нормас у на ужин и переживает
their shots  who is there rules and you do not
их шо те кого есть там правит а ты на
foresee, that is, it’s called so
предвидеть то есть называется так тащить
it’s time to drag home the vital on and the loader just
пора домой виталя на и загрузчик просто
look for the cob like
поищите початок типа
who you can knock down the taste of the birthday
кого можно вкус день роджения сбить и
and so I think to give on promote so that the
так и думаю на дать на продвигаете чтобы
standard May as you could and the
стандартный мая как ты мог бы и вельде
velde but succumb to babble and  I accept so
но поддаваться лопочут и приемлю так
now the issued clans were selling counter
сейчас выданная кланы продавала контр
us there according to the plan to access damask steel.
нас туда по план до доступ булат т.к.
here you are a thousand Russian bones of a kilogram, but then you can’t find all of them a kilogram of tiksi nightingales, you interrupted the counteroffensive with a porsche and a tribute to calla patcha elk in a mix of really kingdoms funny offset crests here, in short, the loss of almost 100 thousand people is waiting for them there 10 others ridiculed that there was nothing shorter, they denied everything in order not to date the Ukrainians to Ukrainians at all where we still have all sorts of their chosen forces there at first, but why did our robots throw such topics so that throw 2 Zelinsky because he just throws at the slaughter of the children of these people by us in order to show some results by the Americans, and so on, then it changed to this no pablo clinic in a panic but there was a clinic edge panic panic still bulan token orbit scroll but also started Belarus on the Ukrainian market already seemed to think that Belarus and the adoration of Belarus in the sun you won’t be here, all the projects didn’t bachila that that Muscovite Amir Andreyka even from him  ismail khan is open on the narrow bridge,
андрейка даже от ним покрыт узкому мосту
look if I had
исмаил хан смотрите если бы у меня вот
this button you were here yes and I don’t
эта кнопка вы тут было да и это я не
press it I would answer kuyava damn it yes dude
нажимай я бы куявы ответил блин да чувак
now I’m finishing the booker shorter now and I’ll press
сейчас я доем букер короче ща и и нажму
it but I don’t have such a button I think
его но у меня нет такой кнопки я думаю
that the blow to  the Crimean bridge will be
что удар по крымскому мосту будет тогда
when Ukraine will have the opportunity to drink according to the
когда украины будут возможности пить по
Crimean now
крымскому сейчас
technical, as I understand it, to the technical
технических как я понимаю до технических
capabilities of an effective strike, well,
возможностей эффективного удара да ну
it’s not even just that we don’t have you there for
что даже не просто надо там вас на
fictitious strikes as
фиктивные удара у нашей стороны нет как
soon as they are, I
только будут я
’m sure that our chosen one will not miss
уверена что наш избранницы не упустить
such a power for her husband  the waves would be holy so
мужу власти такого свята бы волны так
we know from our Crimea
мы знаем из нашего крыма
for rats new children 1 6 in yes and lasts
для крыс новых детьми 1 6 в да и длится
many rich no one seems to be
многие богатому никто кажется не
required there by young people, that is, the letter t,
требоваться там молодью то есть буква т
but you’re nothing there, Sasha, like a drama, a
но ты ничего там саша якоже драма
girl threw thousands of tens of thousands of
закидал девица тысячи десятки тысяч
people and the rich to her husband  why even tedx Russians
людей и богатых зачем даже tedx россиян
and cysts washed their faces with stoned non-scientist
и кист умывалась упоротых не ученый змеи
quiet snakes doubted
тихие сомневалась
them why or scoop up water there will be a
них зачем или зачерпнуть воды будут
tank for yakov
бачек якову но и через джуном с детьми
it’s clear how people
сдашь доплачу воспринимается как люди
were like these two here it is said in the
были таковы два этих здесь говорится в
report to talk about
докладе на говорить о
so
так
128 brigade respect and turn and the
128 бригады респект и повернуть и
desired 120 ma brigade to you and mikhail
желаемое 120 ма бригада вам их и михаил
anton
антон
pass on respect so come off lads
передай респект так отрываетесь хлопцы
juma then you know the Ukrainian blogger
джума то и вы знаете украинскую блогер
openly jigulina
открыто jigulina
barrels in the comments manneredly there are six
бочки в комментарях манерно там шесть
wrote exchanged them miss bates mlm from her and
писал обменял их мисс бейтс млм из нее и
nps to throw us his e-mail socks
нпсов чтобы нас кинул свой e-mail носки
on captcha exchanged we know yes
на капче обменялась мы ну так знаю да
there are necks klim john’s heart and
там шеи клим сердце джона и касянчук
kasyanchuk  thought
для мастики на так менендес т.к. думка
pendants breaks through them child click on
кулоны пробивается им дитя нажми по
throws and I'm a children's film wedding in a
метает и я детский фильм свадьба в
robin flowers a man the power changes
малиновке цветки мужик власть меняется
such woke up the taste and there are cool so I
таких будил на вкус а там крутые так я
respect his skins I will be your look
кого уважает его скильки буду ваш взгляд
and the sea damn you so know about it it
и морю по блин вы так знает об это это
wouldn't be me like this  risky expert
не бы я вот такие рисковые эксперт
erected a new mist on booze and jolt i would
возвели new mist на пьянки и джолт я бы
we were in any no growth you are
мы ни был в каких либо никакого роста вы
now releasing two or three weeks before and we
сейчас выпуска две-три недели до и мы
will release the ruble
рубль будет освобожден
once the truth is well i can’t pull them out for
раз правде ну я не может вытянуть их
rent i yesterday will drag us yesterday there you
напрокат я вчера утянет мы вчера там ты
are there  one is chosen, I experienced
же там один это вот выбран испытала
how easy it would be to take and there is a shorter
насколько просто буду взять и там короче
balakley, so it teaches him, well, maybe he
балаклее так вот учит ну может ему что я
doesn’t know the operational situation of the main
не владею оперативную обстановку мэнэ
nem and until the staff member of the knowledge in the Ministry of Culture
нэма и до штатник знаний в минкульте на
to find what he won’t say there are
это найти к чему не скажет там стоят
such risks there such there such I’m on my feet
такие риска там такие там такие я ноге
to the specialists of yana of my profile saints
специалистам яны моей профильную святые
in order to immediately mid and these nuances,
для то чтобы сразу мид и этих нюансов
so I think that ours and our
так я думаю еще наши с нашим
command will light up the kiss,
командованием кисну прикурить
NATO consultants give what
натовские консультанты дайте то что
helps the plan, and you and the magicians of Tibet can be seen
помогаете плану а ты и маги тибета видно
reconnaissance so I still think
разведку так я думаю еще
ours will not be stormed head-on from
наши не буду тесь как в лоб штурму от
this I am the peasants and storming and storming
этом я крестьян и штурму и штурмует
just like that where 6 such as this price
просто так куда 6 такие как этого цена
was terminals and will give barbecue to you will return
была клеммы и даст шашлык к вам вернется
please tell me what will happen Miss
скажите пожалуйста что случится мисс
Crimea that the majority of Crimeans
крыма что большинство крымчанам
voted for Rashka in  in the fourteenth year
голосовали за рашку в четырнадцатом году
I am 17 I still don’t understand why the
мне 17 я до сих пор не понимаю чего
Russian language culture began to penetrate
русской культуры язык стали проникать
my house 9
мой дом 9
we don’t know
мы не знаем
if the majority of the Crimeans voted for the infection
голосовала ли большинства крымчан заразу
in the fourteenth year because
в четырнадцатом году так потому что
no referendum so legally
никакого референдума так законно там не
took place there there was a sabbath under the
происходило там происходил шабаш под
muzzle of an automatic machine, that is, if  from the very
дулами автомат а то есть если с первых
first days of the occupation there, it was not possible for him
же дней оккупации там нем не было
to hold even
возможности проводить даже проукраинские
some kind of pro-Ukrainian rallies, so for the Ukrainian flag,
какие-то митинги так за флаг украинские
these were taken away and, let’s say, repressed,
там эти отбирали и скажем репрессировали
what kind of public children can we
то про какую публичную дети с мы можем
talk about, that is, people who were
говорить так то есть люди которые были
zuhras, they simply did not show up
зухры они просто не показывались
absolutely that’s why  I say that the
абсолютно так поэтому говорю чтоб
Crimeans, in the fourteenth, the majority
крымчане это в четырнадцатом большинство
voted for Raska, this is nonsense, so
проголосовало за рашку эта брехня так
if we see  that our voting,
если мы видим что наше голосование
which was until 2014 for
которые были до 2014 года за
pro-Russian parties,
пророссийские партии
Russian blocs, all sorts of garbage voted
русские блоки всякое то фигня голосовала
there something of the order of two percent, only the
там что-то порядка двух процентов только
rest of the people voted for
людей остальные голосовали за
pro-Russian but Utkin, not even
пророссийских но уткин даже не
pro-Russian vodka, let's say
пророссийские водки скажем
no-no-no-not Ukraine centric just the
не-не-не-не украина центрических просто
effect of the Party of Regions  in tampa flexible
эффекте партии регионов в тампе гибкий
so on
так дальше
so to say that they
поэтому говорить что
voted for rashka it's wrong
голосовали за рашку это неправильно
no one knows what tone of voice you can
никто не знаю что тон голоса вы можете
see the ticket not in the archive of
посмотреть билет не в архиве
money no one until they showed you came by
денег никто не пока вам показали пришел
referendum showed the results searched for the
референдумом показали результаты искали
majority voted everything
большинство проголосовало все
so compress the movie 2 1 3 baby
так кино сжимаем 2 1 3 малютка
goncharenko they will flow away  now also 3
гончаренко их утекут сейчас тоже 3
live badge someone on the network people so
прямой эфир бляха хто в сети люди так
my relatives in simferopol 2 how yours will
меня родичи в симферополе 2 як ваш
stay adab 20 before the Ukrainian language is her
побуду адаб 20 до украинской мовы это ее
friend at
подруга у его
his discount you are a friend of an adept and a
на скидки вас подруга адепту и
good friend adapter let's say it's easier
хорошая подруга адаптер скажем так легче
spar glumov Ukrainian at 5 at least think
шпат глумова украинском на 5 хоть думаем
about you will
о
learn  there
выучишь там
with enough mori mine there and one so
с достаточно mori mine там а один так
you can co and run it
можешь со и запустит она побачення от и
we’ll say further like this, God’s connect
поговорим далее вот так божия connect
washed the time, we still this pipe will
умылась тайме мы еще эта труба будет
hold on cipro Crimean mist so a
держаться cipro крымский mist так
second second
секундочку секунду
so
так
Andreeva
андреева
slipped through this manycha so I want
этом проскочил маныча так хочу
to see all of yours, since you ask,
повидаться на все ваши , раз вы задаёте
it means that you are asking them a price, so
значит вас им натикало цену так что
you don’t think about Karabakh, can you be the
думаете вы не об карабахе сможет ли
first  Karabakh as a whole I’m not an expert
первыми карабах целиком я не экспертом
in the military there, the more so I
там военным тем больше так вами я
put pressure on your veins and the
надавите на вены и
logic is like that, but the thrush Azerbaijan
логика такая все а дрозда азербайджан
bead and Natash’s faces are sent in the
буса и лица-то речи наташ посылается в
region there, I think I’ll
регионе там у я думаю еще
turn the Karabakh found,
повернуть найденного карабаху , часу
it’s only an hour
лишь это
so the
так так
hippopotamus cat Andreev will have  even
кот бегемот андреевым окажет еще
mayonnaise to machines in the haze horde of russia in
майонеза машинам в дымку орда россии в
ukraine and also a house of a nuclear button you
украине а еще домик ядерной кнопки ты
will be a gas tap cat hippopotamus checks
будет газовый кран кот бегемот чеках
excitement in ukraine in ukraine so the most with
азарт в украине в украине так самый с
vegetables shows
овощи показы
fishing wisdom you can build an account
промысла wisdom можно построение счет
this year on fell and not so it
это году на упал и не так будет так
will be a problem for rent reasonable for
будет проблема напрокат разумное для
can someone wish, that is,
можно кто-то пожелал то есть нам
Azovstal chewed gas for us, chewed on fangs,
азовсталь пожевала газ жевала на клыки
your monsters are here to knock the
монстры ваши здесь стукнуть с перебоями
Turks intermittently, but for  we own I think
турки врази а для нас own я думаю году
you stole less from us, but gays have power over
вы стащили меньше у нас же геи властны
gas profit when extracting files or
газу выгоду при добывании на файлам или
I think so there at Yana I think we will still have
мне так там у яны думаю еще у нас будет
such a direct catastrophe ecologists worm
прям такая катастрофа экологи червеца
communal so yes there will be economy from you
коммунально так да будут эконом от вас
at least where else you have a centralized
хоть куда еще у вас централизованного
floor  get it wrong I would like to see you
пола не добудет не так я к вам бы
so all-ins will freeze
хотелось так олл-ины замерзнет
so
так
andrey you know the blogger of the brand of tea you know
андрей знаете блогера марки чая знаете
where he was from the barrel in a fit of commercials you
где он был из бочки порыве ролики
fit in ministries
вписываешься ministries ты кому-то
hello from germany
дьяков будет вольной привет из германии
can’t be found on may 3 i.e. oh slow
не найти на 3 мая то есть о медленно
good food clearly stock lab assistant
хорошее питание четко штока лаборанта
stream from stream u sleep at prices before planted [ __ ] he needs to go
стриму со стрима у сон в цены до
to jail so then reception sbu so there and that
в тюрьму так то прием сбу так там и что
when these pro-russian all sorts of topics for a
when these пророссийские всякие темы
long time just shaft screws  of the simplest
давно просто вал винтах самого простого
eraser wounds, the virus is not all movement so before the
ластик ран вирус не все движухи так до
building of Russian curators, it’s clear that
зданием российских кураторов это ясно
Bulavin was even sharks, those who
булавин даже был акулы тех
strained
напрягалась в
20 times will be able to brehat or maybe not
20 раз на будут может брехать а может и
and despite the fact that it has become so easy for him to make
на виду при том что даст ему стало так
such a breakthrough to ideality
просто таких лет прорыв к идеальности
that he is little closed at the same time, 3-4
что его его мало закрыты при этом 3-4
rocks are like a thought of food from 3 musala dotse apples and practitioners of our special services,
доце яблоки и практик наших спецслужб
we can wine Aries, maybe he specifically
кача можем вин овен может специально
knows to report to us there  like at
знает доложить я нам там типа на
first you are not such a
перво ты такого не
real [ __ ] so easy to
реального дебила так просто чтобы
turn them open and clowning
претворить их открыть и клоунада
so
так
olga capricorn writes 990 lunch friend to
ольга козерог пишет 990 друга обеда на
mobile
мобиль
mobile team something ember
мобильная бригада чему-то эмбер также
will also take vibrato there every trigger max
примет там вибрато каждый триггер максу
olga brother put rex 90 other mbr don’t
брат ольги кладу rex 90 другой mbr не
know breathe can store  you succumb to the
знаете надышать может запасти поддаешься
grafted detailed and all your
привитыми детальная и всем твоим
brigade combo of ours for the dacha, and someone
бригадный комбик наших для дачи а кто-то
try the [ __ ] optimal one view or over the
трымай письку optimal один вид или над
west all not up to thanks to the
west all не до благодаря карабас
accusatory karabas you don’t know all the bloggers
обвинительная не знаете всех блогеров
there karabas
там карабас барабас скидки ты даже не
barabas  apply myself generation 30 + so
чем применяться собой поколение 30 + так
obviously respect you Odessa
явно уважаю вас одесскую хунту
intellectual junta less than 500 will answer in
интеллектуала меньше 500 ответят в
Ukrainian I share teach in letka I eat
украинский я делюсь учат в летки ем рис
nist rice or
nist или
other  there were hiccups to steal there, so those
приколисты есть угонять там шел так этих
who we like the
кто нам нравится
idea from her to this is logical and
мысль от ее к этому логично и западню
trap with this with the right dubko we are for the dacha
вот этим с правильными дубко мы для дачи
and you are what a gvor and just 4-ki there so
и ты каким гворий и просто там 4-ки так
basically I still love
принципе я обожаю еще
life genres to my what else is there let it be
жизни жанры моему чему там еще вот пусть
whom the sky will blow very much, I there the size of the
и кого подует весьма небо я там размер
rugs is standardly closed to the shaft, and who
коврики стандартно закрываю валу а кто
wants just a song of God's day,
хочет просто песня божкова дня
spread out just sell everyone who is a
разложите просто продают все кто моря
prison for the project, so I want to blow with the
тюрьму на проект так вот хочу подует
effect of the mother at the edge of the ninth floor, the grass is
эффектом мать у края девятом этаже трава
so torment for normal and massacre genres of
так мук для нормальной и резни жанры
cinema there is a comedy melodrama
кино там комедия мелодрама
I  so I will send sunbeds and melodrama
я так вот я направлю лежаки и мелодрама
I love comedies comedy films
я люблю комедии приходные фильмы
fantasy love scenes means that there is no
фантастику люблю сцены значит что нет
slave to make films of compression than for the right
раба снимать фильмы сжатия чем на право
to engage in melodramas like
заниматься мелодрам как на
that such people cinema spooky was nine
то такие люди кино spooky был девять
centuries old
веков
I found a treasure on what the principle covers the
дуже клад нашел на чем принцип покрывает
carved spectrum of the genre and the skin of Nukve  no at
резные спектр жанре и кожи нукве нет на
and leisure due to the future so the accuracy of
и досуге счет будущей так точность
reasonable accuracy of weights that is, just
разумных точность весовых то есть просто
choke on dopam swells on the Muscovite I will
подавиться допам отекает на москаля я
connect less I will go py  ncheon
подключить меньше буду идти pyncheon
cartoon before the
мультика до
gangway this is the view it’s so hello I
трапа это вид у это так алло я всячески
remember my soul in every possible way and what we want to rub it not
помин души и что мы хочем руб это не
only knows but there it was washed decomposed
просто знает а там подмылась разложилось
who you don’t cut and snake and in our
кому вы не рубит и змеиной и в нашему
trail finally through t content and in
следу ваще через t контент и в ихнем
theirs I’ll die a boob
умру сиську
so they always know and  needles of goods
так всегда знают и хвои товаров
notifies and his rock
уведомляет и его рок
so in russia a man a sign of protest against the
так в россии мужик знак протеста против
war jock of his son's passport in the evening
войны джок паспорта своей сына вечером
son dad where is my passport dad
сынок папа где мой паспорт папа
character and rims cat hippopotamus
характером и закраины кот бегемот дякую
for calmly you grass we can u no one will
за спокойно вы травы мы можем у никто не
give smoke from cops
даст дым от ментами
new nickname venus in the center of europe
new ник венера в центре европы
bachy attacks of the stars kapets bachyly the queen of
бача атаки звезд капец бачылы королева
england died there can’t be the stage the
англии померла там не может будет этапе
same ringing you
таки звон вы направо
rightly read Senka and the test for
почитала сенька так и испытание для
honoring England examples I intend
почитаться англии примеров я намерен
to do in england in general on the cable and
таки в англии вообще на кабель и
I know there in the sim card received to the elevator
знаю там в полученному к лифту
we repulsed the balakleya cheers god bless
симку наши отбили балаклея ура храни бог
our soldiers  let their bullets go.
наших солдат пусть пули их не буду .
our ours is that our ukrainian friends
наши наши это что наши украинские друзья
whose write beat back the baht on the glue
которого пишите отбили бат на клей
i am 15 bloggers answer sensors normal
я 15 блогера отвечать датчики нормальный
man the goal is more older wines that
мужик цель вин побольше постарше that
when so advantageous promise grandfather
when так выгодой обещание дедушка еще
one more thing from her chest so type and at
одну вещь от ее на груди так типа и под
an angle from cool men is not befitting
углом от прикольно мужчинам не подобает
so only there
так только там
elizaveta palermo there and it will be possible for you to make
елизавета палермо там и можно будет вы
fun of it, you need
прикалываетесь надо
to touch it further there or for that,
трогать именно дальше там или за этого
but there is a possibility of feeling that an independent republic will become an
но так есть вероятность ощущения станет
independent republic, the rest of the
независимой республики остальные
republics will either become walls of failure,
республики стенок отказов будет либо
yes, I think that the
станет да я думаю что
movement in the Caucasus is a matter of time, the empire is understood to be the Caucasus, this
движуха на кавказе это вопрос времени
is
ослабляется империя понимается кавказ
a classic,
это классика
so it is and  it was 96 hands the blind
так есть и было 96 руки the blind
increased with the light of the world we already
возросла при зиле света мы уже два раза
told about elizaveta twice on the cob of the
про елизавету рассказал на початку
streamer said and just that
стримера сказал и просто что елизавета
elizaveta helped stanadyne how did you come Chuvash
помогла stanadyne как пришел вы чуваши
or two stages
или два этапа марилла метки блин да
comes to damn
на запись меня мы не приходит к блин
elizabeth is dead i
елизавета умерла я
don't give up that mouse skin elizaveta
не сдается что кожи мыши елизавета
paper on pr  from alexey others
бумаги на приз алексей других фейсбуку
wrote to facebook exif twitter
написал exif твиттере
chained his cherkas elizaveta helped
прикован его черкаш елизавета помогла
caps and in short i’m already 1 to 15
шапок и короче я на я уже 1 до 15
feeling today or riding in it
чувство сегодняшний или езда в это
helped i don’t know if it’s real chu
помогло я не знаю то что реально ли чу
chu about or can elizaveta night
чу примерно или можете елизавета ночь
she helped so yuppies but neighbor partially
она помогла так яппи но соседа частично
I’m okay with this
нормально отношусь так
[music]
[музыка]
Andrey, since
андрей так как
food is on the civil right, who can you
питание по цивильных справа хто ж можно
bet you can bet you will be here
ставить вы можете ставить ты тут будете
trying to feed in that match of my battalion commander
пытая питания в том матче моей комбата
Nastya will meet the result for a
насти будут встречать результата на
headshot I won’t be happy to see such I
хедшот я не буду рад видеть такие я
’ll say the
скажу
same today the whole bad  but after all, an
так же сегодня ушла целая плохо да ведь
era is falling and
падает эпоха и
somehow good people are building eras and
добрый как-то то люди строя эпох и
this means that a place is opening up for
подходит это значит и открывается место
new young people and creating a husband
новым молодым и создать изминает мужу
crushing young scizor children on people of a new
молодей scizor детьми на люди нового
generation still old people don’t forever
поколения еще старые люди не завжды
head off rusticity you don’t go out zmin
башку простоватость ты не выходишь змин
want reforms from 60 to me  rumpled injections I
хочешь реформ от 60 до я помятой уколы я
was small and at school c
был мал и в школе c
class 5 d 92 league and
class 5 д 92 лигу и
hostesses at 4 o’clock wrote and with ink
хозяйки в 4 ч писал и чернильными
pens showed
ручками показал еще
ballpoint pens height distance  oh, the
шариковым культуры ручкам высоты отстой
handwriting on such calligraphy is not so, but in
почерк на такие каллиграфии не так а а
ink it’s bulo that such a rope of a
вот чернилами було что такая канат
glass is what
бокала чем
I do
я
cdh whether the handles people guess and the
цдх ли ручки люди вот загадайте и
cuirass model turn back this is to
кирас модель возвертайтесь это чтоб
height the pen and to give me about the flowers
высоты ручку и чтобы дать мне про цветы
installed filled out from the
установлены заполнен таки из документа
food document eat into the bay same view off  and the height
пищи съедай в залив же вид выкл и высота
from her husband is a citron molded by
от мужа цитрон формуется
mine, he’s not a fact about the king, the younger is purely Chopin,
моей он не факт о короле младшой чисто
damn it, there’s a problem for you who
шопен блин вот вам проблемах кто там
will become king there, stop grandson, it
стану королем короче перестаньте внук
’s real, but the old [ __ ] is just
вот реально но старая [__] раз потому
because from the armor of the forces of Ukraine, the star than your
что с брони силы украины звезда чем ваш
click is there and it’s expanding,
клик там так и по ширится отирались так
so  there, with the queen, there is a son, a grandson, a brother
что там с королевой там сын внук брат
, they will not figure out their chests, the
вынырнуть грудь в не разберутся им
most prominent of them there, the traditions of the saleswoman of
виднейшие них там традиции продавщицей
Vlad;
украинских рамадан .
Yes,
да окей
ok Andrey, what do you think, Kadyrov will be fired
андрей как вы думаете кадырова уволят
or killed, you are Chechens, Brandon Yes, I
или грохнут вы ж чеченцы брэндон да я
think that such characters as Kadyrov,
думаю что такие персонажи как кадыров
they do not leave because the British
они не уходят так как британская
Queen leaves them earlier,
королева их уходят раньше
ok, let's get tighter for today than the same
окей давай на сегодня все туже дуже
exim who was on the stream today
дякую exim кто был на стриме сегодня у
we had without  roulettes so we were more
нас была без рулетки так мы больше скилл
skillful there even today from the armor of the Ukrainian forces
ковалась там еще сегодня с брони силы
rotted it was honestly part of well, and the
сгнил это было честно части ну да и
Kharkiv region will continue its
харьковской области продолжит св
effective naphtha in Russian all sorts of
эффективный нафту в российских всяких
energetic kilograms droopingly
килограммах энергичных по никам ных
sprinkled all over the front of the tube right there
посыпав все фронт тубу прямо места
write who is boom who is such a
напишите кто такой бум кто такого места
place and  our entire stream and whoever wants to
да и вся наш стрим и кто кто хочет
see it on the pit market channel so maybe
видеть это на пит рынку каналу так может
a sign of the date on the ice over it the screw is
и знака дата льду над он винт
suspended kevin in the inventory
приостановлен kevin в описи
on top of the channel and write who is not the commissioner
сверху канал и напишите кто не комистат
you are all streaming myself I visualized 2 we have sprats
вы все стрим сам я визуал 2 у нас кильки
wide us in Europe with him even  wild
широкого нас в европе с ним даже дикую
I put it on the wound and tomorrow we
я продеваю что на рану и на завтра у нас
will have more cool new aura with it there
будет больше крутых новым ауру с ней
will be burning farts of such signs to the
будут горящие пердаки таких знаков
gates all over the territory of Russia
воротам по всему там территории россии
such  signs fireworks practice not
такие знаки фейерверки практике не в
uphill rams because for false heat and a
гору овны потому что за ложный жар и
coward do not put pressure on the appearance and glory to ukraine
трус не давить на вид и слава украине
this is
это
what it is almost like a shift of the th place
какую она почти что сдвиг о-го-го места
and thermal
и термальная
[music]
[музыка]